// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The operator used to access member function of a structure using its object",
    answer: ".",
    options: [
      ".",
      "->",
      "*",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Escape sequence character '\0' occupies __ amount of memory",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "0",
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the full form of RTTI",
    answer: "Runtime type identification",
    options: [
      "Runtime type identification",
      "Runtime template identification",
      "Robust Template Type Inheritance",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "C++ does not supports the following",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Multilevel inheritance",
      "Hierarchical inheritance",
      "Hybrid inheritance",
      "None of the above"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "An exception is __",
    answer: "Runtime error",
    options: [
      "Runtime error",
      "Compile time error",
      "Logical error",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Identify the C++ compiler of Linux",
    answer: "g++",
    options: [
      "cpp",
      "Borland",
      "vc++",
      "g++"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Why is a class useful in programming?",
    answer: "permit data to be hidden from other classes",
    options: [
      "are removed from memory when not in use",
      "permit data to be hidden from other classes.",
      "bring together all aspects of an entity in one place",
      "can closely model objects in the real world"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which type of data file is analogous to an audio cassette tape?",
    answer: "Sequential access file",
    options: [
      "Random access file",
      "Binary file",
      "Source code file",
      "Sequential access file"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following statements is true about inline functions?",
    answer: "It's a request to the compiler to make the function inline",
    options: [
      "It's a compulsion on the compiler to make a function inline",
      "It's a request to the compiler to make the function inline",
      "It's the indication to the compiler that the function is recursive.",
      "It's the indication to the compiler that the function is a member function"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What happens when an argument is passed by reference?",
    answer: "A variable is created within the function to hold the argument value",
    options: [
      "A temp variable is created in the calling program to hold arguments value",
      "None",
      "A variable is created within the function to hold the argument value",
      "The function can't access the argument value"
    ]
  },

];